<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Javascript基础 on</title><link>/js/basic/</link><description>Recent content in Javascript基础 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/js/basic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>javascript介绍</title><link>/js/basic/javascript%E4%BB%8B%E7%BB%8D/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/js/basic/javascript%E4%BB%8B%E7%BB%8D/</guid><description>What is JavaScript? # JavaScript is a high-level, dynamic, lightweight, interpreted computer programming language. It’s designed for creating network-centric apps. It has made modern web apps possible— apps with which you can interact directly without doing a page reload for every action. It’s also used in more traditional websites to provide different forms of interactivity and cleverness.
JavaScript是一种高级的、动态的、轻量的、解释性的电脑编程语言。它被用来创建以网络中心的应用。它使得创建现代的web应用成为可能，一种你可以直接和页面交互，不需要刷新页面的web应用。它也用在一些传统网站提供不同形式的巧妙的互动效果。
JavaScript is mostly used as a part of web pages. Implementations of JavaScript allow client-side script to interact with the user and make dynamic web pages.</description></item><item><title>使用javascript</title><link>/js/basic/%E4%BD%BF%E7%94%A8javascript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/js/basic/%E4%BD%BF%E7%94%A8javascript/</guid><description>Writing Your First JavaScript Program # HTML can’t do the math, it can’t figure out if someone has correctly filled out a form. HTML just let people read the text, watch videos, look at pictures, and click links. You need JavaScript to add intelligence to your web pages so they can respond to your site’s visitors. So JavaScript lets you make your websites more attractive, effective, and useful.
JavaScript is more complex than HTML or CSS, the main goal of this book is to help you think more like a programmer.</description></item><item><title>JS注释</title><link>/js/basic/js%E6%B3%A8%E9%87%8A/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/js/basic/js%E6%B3%A8%E9%87%8A/</guid><description>JavaScript comments # We usually use JavaScript comments for explaining JavaScript code and making it more readable. They also can be used to prevent execution during testing alternative code.
There are exists two types of comments: single line comments and multi-line comments. The example which you see here uses a single-line comment before each code line:
&amp;lt;!DOCTYPE HTML&amp;gt; &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; Javascript comments: // &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; // console.log('Welcome to w3Docs!'); &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/html&amp;gt; We use single line comments for writing small notes.</description></item><item><title>JS操作DOM</title><link>/js/basic/js%E6%93%8D%E4%BD%9Cdom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/js/basic/js%E6%93%8D%E4%BD%9Cdom/</guid><description>What is DOM # The Document Object Model (DOM) is a way to represent a programming interface for HTML and XML documents. With the help of DOM we can gain and manipulate tags, classes using commands of Documents object. It gives an opportunity to connect programming languages to the page.
DOM Document # Web page is a document, which we can display in the browser window or as the HTML source.</description></item></channel></rss>